doublerobotics.com 2018-10-17

# Double Robotics - Telepresence Robot for Telecommuters

### Privacy Policy

Your privacy is critically important to us. At Double Robotics, Inc., we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don't ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.
  * We don't share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals:

If you have questions about deleting or correcting your personal data please contact our [support team](http://support.doublerobotics.com/).

Double Robotics, Inc. (“Double Robotics, Inc.”) operates www.doublerobotics.com. It is Double Robotics, Inc.’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website.

#### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Double Robotics, Inc. collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Double Robotics, Inc.'s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Double Robotics, Inc.'s visitors use its website. From time to time, Double Robotics, Inc. may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Double Robotics, Inc. also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Double Robotics, Inc. only discloses logged in user IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.

#### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Double Robotics, Inc.’s website choose to interact with Double Robotics, Inc. in ways that require Double Robotics, Inc. to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Double Robotics, Inc. gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for an account at doublerobotics.com to provide a username and email address. Double Robotics, Inc. collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Double Robotics, Inc.. Double Robotics, Inc. does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

#### Aggregated Statistics

Double Robotics, Inc. may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. However, Double Robotics, Inc. does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

#### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Double Robotics, Inc. discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Double Robotics, Inc.’s behalf or to provide services available at Double Robotics, Inc.’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Double Robotics, Inc.’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Double Robotics, Inc. will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Double Robotics, Inc. discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Double Robotics, Inc. believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Double Robotics, Inc., third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Double Robotics, Inc. website and have supplied your email address, Double Robotics, Inc. may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Double Robotics, Inc. and our products. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Double Robotics, Inc. takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

#### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Double Robotics, Inc. uses cookies to help Double Robotics, Inc. identify and track visitors, their usage of Double Robotics, Inc. website, and their website access preferences. Double Robotics, Inc. visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Double Robotics, Inc.’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Double Robotics, Inc.’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

#### Business Transfers

If Double Robotics, Inc., or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Double Robotics, Inc. goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Double Robotics, Inc. may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

#### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Double Robotics, Inc. may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Double Robotics, Inc.’s sole discretion. Double Robotics, Inc. encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy.Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
